Carl Owen Dunbar Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
- Miscellaneous, Series IV
  - Collection Information. Collection lists, notes and inventories., 001195
    - Inventory of Fred Braun Collection after arrival at Yale., 1931; 000238
    - Notes on collections by Danish expeditions: Greenland., 000221
    - Notes on YPM fusulinid collection; YPM types, 000245
    - Notes on YPM fusulinid collection with locality descr., 000246
    - Catalog of Undergraduate Teaching Collection - Nautiloidea, Ammonoidea, Gastropoda, Bivalvia, Trilobita, Ostracoda, Bryozoa (formerly doc. 155); (+ dissociated specimen labels. see also doc. 362)., 000328
  - Correspondence., 001196
    - Papers, notes, correspondence. Correspondence, memos and notes pertaining to the "Pseudoschwagerina stanislavi" problem. 1944-1953., 002421
    - Papers, notes, correspondence. Correspondence, memos and notes pertaining to Walcott medal for 1962 which was presented to A.A. Opik. 1961-1962, 000711
  - Locality Information. Miscellaneous locality catalogs., 001194
    - Catalog of localities. Catalog of localities: Alabama, Florida., 1966; 000160
    - Catalog of localities. Catalog of L. Koch's Permian localities: Greenland., 000223
    - Guidebook. Field Guidebook & Catalog of Tertiary type localities: Alabama, Mississippi., 1955; 000055
    - Locality information. locality information; Georgia., 1965; 000490
    - Locality information. Catalog of W. Maync's Permian localities: Greenland., 000224
    - List of Pennsylvanian fusulinids YPM 11001 - 11274 with horizon, loc., and coll., from Illinois, Texas, Nebraska, Oklahoma, Missouri, Iowa, Nevada, Bolivia, from many different accns (probably related to paper by Dunbar on fusulinids of Nebraska). 1928 +/-5, 000406
    - List of Goniatite Zones, England., 1948; 000370
  - Miscellaneous. Miscellaneous archives including unpublished work, memorabilia, guidebooks, and other material., 001197
    - Manuscript material. Unpublished MS by Dunbar on "Exothecal tissue in the Archeocyathidae": & black ane white negatives and prints of YPM 17047 (Exocyathus regularis), 1963; 000760
    - Miscellaneous. Memorabilia; including transcript of taped interview done by K.M. Waage, certificates, newspaper articles, photographs, etc., 2003; 000775
    - Miscellaneous. C. O. Dunbar's personal "encyclopedia" consisting of index card notes. Notes cover published references to many taxonomic groups, stratigraphic periods, and geographic regions, as well as some newspaper and article clippings. This collection is also referred to as "WikiDunbar" and "Dunbarpedia." 19 envelopes., 002422
    - Miscellaneous. 2 boxes of black and white lantern slides - "Permian faunas." These include figures, photos, and fossil plates. (14 slides in total)., 002423
    - Copies of excursion guidebooks for the 17th International Geological Congress, Russia., 1937; 000368
    - Class notes (4 notebooks) by C.V.A. [Catherine (Bobby) Van Aken (Smith)], Invertebrate Paleontology & Invertebrate Zoology. 1947-1949, 000706
    - removed to IPAR.000328, 000155
    - List of the distribution of Flexibilia Crinoids by genus., 002694